Aaron Graham

Laborer - Operator Forklift-Warehouse

Fort Smith, AR 72901 aaron.graham1978@gmail.com (479)-259-3474

I have 10 years of experience, as a Laborer, as an Operator/Laborer and as a Delivery Driver in industries including Construction Special Trade Contractors, Wholesale Trade-Durable Goods and Automotive Dealers and Gasoline Service Stations. Most recently, I have been working as a forklift operator at Planters foods in the shipping department. My skills and experiences include: Hoisting Equipment, Shipping.

Willing to relocate to: Van Buren, AR - Fort Smith, AR Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Warehouse Worker

Burford Distribution - Fort Smith, AR June 2018 to Present

Alcohol Distribution and service pull orders for next day deliveries

Forklift Operator/Warehouse

Zero Mountain - Fort Smith, AR February 2016 to April 2018

Forklift certification

Forklift Operator

Planters Foods for Kelly Services - Fort Smith, AR August 2015 to February 2016

Responsibilities

Put up pallets from production to the warehouse in to racking systems loading and unloading trucks using computers to properly scan pallets to a location.

Logs and bill of lading enter in ship trucks in computer,

Accomplishments

Ability to safely operate a forklift putting away different types of products and forklift certification.

Laborer/Operator

Sun Valley Masonry - Edmond, OK September 2014 to December 2014

Performed physical tasks for projects such as building, highway, heavy construction, excavation, demolition. Cleaned and prepared sites. Dug trenches. Set braces to support excavation sides. Put up and took down scaffolding, shoring, braces, traffic barricades, ramps, temporary devices. Cleaned up rubble and debris. Assisted other craft workers. Read and interpreted plans, instructions, specs, blueprints. Helped operators align, move and adjust machines, equipment, materials. Designated

construction work areas. Loaded and unloaded building materials, machinery, tools. Identified and distributed building materials to appropriate locations.

Operator/Laborer

International Installation Group - Stillwater, OK July 2014 to September 2014

Performed manual labor. Determined work assignments and equipment needs. Loaded and unloaded materials. Operated winches and hoisting devices. Moved materials on worksites. Moved materials by hand, using heavy equipment. Assembled product containers. Reported shortages and damaged materials. Inventoried materials. Ensured a clean and safe working environment. Performed housekeeping duties. Maintained tools and equipment.

Delivery Driver

Direct Discount Tire - Stillwater, OK April 2014 to July 2014

Delivered products/services including: Tires, Tubes, Wheels, Valve Stems, etc. Collected money from customers, made change, and recorded sales. Travelled set routes to provide services. Informed regular customers of new products, services, and promotions. Completed customer orders and sales contracts. Recorded daily sales and delivery information. Determined delivery routes. Built and maintained quality customer relationships. Inspected vehicles daily. Loaded and unloaded vehicle. Valid driver's license. Maintained clean driving record.

Assembly Line Worker

Ditch Witch - Perry, OK August 2013 to April 2014

Made necessary adjustments to machines. Set up machines. Checked work pieces for defects, accuracy. Operated machines, including lathes, cutters, shears, millers, grinders, presses, drills, heating machines. Read and interpreted blueprints, work orders, charts, diagrams. Made metal work pieces. Positioned work pieces. Replaced worn machine pieces. Notified supervisors when major repairs are required. Turned on machines. Performed machine maintenance. Lubricated parts. Operate forklifts, man lifts wiz bangs other vehicles performing parts delivery and made sure right amount of that part are present in work areas.

Operator/Laborer

JLT Contracting - Cushing, OK June 2013 to April 2014

Performed physical tasks for projects such as highway, heavy construction, excavation, demolition. Cleaned and prepared sites. Dug trenches. Set braces to support excavation sides. Put up and took down scaffolding, shoring, braces, traffic barricades, ramps, temporary devices. Cleaned up rubble and debris. Read and interpreted plans, instructions, specs, blueprints. Decided on work activities. Controlled traffic in and around work zones. Helped operators align, move and adjust machines, equipment, materials. Positioned and sealed structural components such as pipes. Designated construction work areas.

Preventive Maintenance Technician/Shipping and Recieving forklift operator Shipping Lead

Tyson Foods, Inc - Russellville, AR January 2005 to March 2012

Responsibilities

Repaired and maintained the following Mack, Peteerbuilt, International Trucks, Travis, East, Tibrook, Summit, Ledwell and Dorsey trailers.

Changed and replaced brakes and repair axles. Experienced in electrical repair, mechanical repair, alignment. Maintained hydraulic and pneumatic systems, gas and diesel equipment, AC/DC systems. Inspected and tested equipment. Replaced worn and broken parts. Used hand tools, power tools, precison measuring instruments. Electrical and electonic testing devices, hoists, lifts, pullers. Took apart and reassembled equipment checked and changed fluids such as oil hydaulic fluid, antifreeze, gear oil, replaced tires and wheels when needed. Performed Preventive Maintainance.

Shipping/recieving lead loaded and unloaded trucks loaded blast cells and railcars staged products with stamps for overseas shippments.

Accomplishments
Forklift certified
Air brake repair certification through Mack dealer

Education

High school or equivalent in General Studies

Paris High School - Paris, AR 1995 to 1997

Skills

Warehouse Inventory Forklift Shipping/Recieving, Forklift and Manlift Certified through Hertz Rental, Forklift, Forklift Driver, Reach Truck, Reach, Warehouse Associate, Picker Packer, Shipping Receiving, Order Puller, Shipping, Loading

Certifications/Licenses

Forklift Operator

August 2015 to August 2018

Additional Information

Skills

ac/dc, demolition, grinders, hand tools, heavy equipment, hoisting equipment, housekeeping, lathes, machinery, power tools, preventive maintenance, repair, sales, shipping, forklift certification including sky tracks, lull, genie, man lift certification, DOT health card. I also grew up on a cattle farm operated tractors, balers, mowers backhoes, dozers, trackhoe 15 years of experience in farming taking care of cattle, horses, pigs, chickens, dogs and cats.Baiing hay and taking care and hauling equipment.